localwineevents.com 2012-10-04

# Our Privacy Policy: LocalWineEvents.com : Wine, Food, Beer, Or Spirits

## Our Privacy Policy

### Effetive Date: 2/9/2007

Our Policy. 

LocalWineEvents.com respects and understands its website users' concerns about confidentiality and privacy, and we take reasonable steps to ensure that any information you give us is handled in a safe and responsible manner. Because of our respect and understanding, we have developed this Privacy Policy which discloses the privacy practices of LocalWineEvents.com and describes the information we collect about you during your use of our site and what use we may make of that information. 

It is important to remember that by using our site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We suggest that you refer to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis as it may change, at any time at LocalWineEvents.com's sole discretion, in order to allow us to take advantage of any technological advances or for business purposes or legal reasons. 

Information That We May Collect. 

We collect your information in different areas of our site. The exact information collected varies depending on the areas of our site that you use. For example, when you complete any forms on the site, we may require that you provide us with your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. If you do not want to provide us with this information or any other requested information, please do not complete any forms. Additionally, the site may allow you to voluntarily disclose information to us through a survey or in an email. 

In the course of using our site, we may also automatically track certain information about you. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address. Many sites automatically collect this information. We do not collect or use this information to create a profile about you. We also use cookies on our site. Cookies can help us provide information which is targeted to your interests. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. 

Our Use of Your Information. 

We internally use personally identifiable information to improve our goods and services, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content, to customize our site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. We may also disclose or use personally identifiable information to investigate and respond to any violations of our website Terms of Use. 

We do not sell, lend or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third parties outside of LocalWineEvents.com, its parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, authorized agents and service providers, operating companies and other related entities. We only disclose information to third parties when it is reasonably necessary in order to allow us to provide information, goods or services that have been requested by users. 

We may also use personally identifiable information to deliver information that, in some cases, is targeted to your needs and interests, such as promotional e-mails, targeted banners and promotions. If you supply us with your e-mail or mailing address, you may receive occasional mail from us announcing services, product information, promotional events or updates to our website. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please send us an e-mail to [Info@LocalWineEvents.com](mailto:Info@LocalWineEvents.com) indicating your e-mail address or mailing address as applicable and asking us to remove you from our mailing list. Also, if at any time you no longer wish to receive such e-mail from us, you can click the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of every issue of The Juice that you receive. That link is specific to you and one-click deletes your email immediately and completely from our database. 

In the event our company is ever sold, we reserve the right to transfer ownership of our e-mail list and other personally identifiable information to the acquiring company. 

We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you as required by law, including voluntary disclosures to law enforcement agencies and government officials, as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. 

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), third parties may unlawfully intercept or access files, transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect personally identifiable information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. 

Third Party Collectors of Information. 

Our Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that your information is disclosed by you to third parties, whether our clients, service providers, advertisers or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of your information. These third parties adhere to their own privacy customs and policies. Because we do not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. We do not make any representations or warranties as to how such third parties may use your information. 

Notification of Material Changes to this Policy 

This Section identifies material changes to this Policy since the Effective Date. 

(None at present.) 

Contacting the Site. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to review, change or remove your personal information, you can e-mail us at [Info@LocalWineEvents.com](mailto:Info@LocalWineEvents.com)

You can make changes under "My Account". 

Click "Member Login" on the left and log in using the info you registered with. Your username will be your email and password would be included in the confirmation email you received from Local Wine Events.com.  
If you don't know your password, enter your email here, <http://www.localwineevents.com/account/acct_forgot.php> After you hit enter, it will say, (on the left), Hello  and a link for "My Account". Under My Account will be your settings for The Juice. 

If at any time you no longer wish to receive such e-mail from us, you can click the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of every issue of The Juice that you receive. That link is specific to you and one-click deletes your email immediately and completely from our database. 

Additionally, you can contact us by writing to: 

Local Wine Events.com  
2042 General Alexander Dr.  
Malvern, PA. 19355  
(610) 647-4888
